



Male 31 Years old (1990/04) Living in Shanghai-Pudong 9 Years

Personal Advantage

Hi, my name is Gethin, a software engineer which has majored in computer science and a lot of working experience in foreig n fin-tech enterprises and famous internet companies like Honeywell, Tencent, etc.

My goal is to be a software architect, I'm good at System Architecture & Refactoring & Design, Technical Research & Selection, Project Risk Identification. I also like research the cloud architect design.

Strong learning capability, efficient communication, agile project management, strong implementation capacity, rapid technol ogy selection is my advantage.

I'm familiar with OOP, SOA, AOP, MVC, MVVM, EDA, BDD, DDD, Micro Service, Cloud Architecture, SPA etc. I value codin g standards based on SOLID and know the common styles of Architecture & UML.

I excellent in C#/.Net Technology, Proficient in traditional .NET Technology like WCF, WEB API, MVC, WPF & .NET COR E, RabbitMQ, Azure, K8S, Docker, etc.

Based on the limit of website, detail info Pls Ref https://blog.gethin.online/en/about/

Recent Work Highest Degree

Position: Sr. Software Engineer Major: Computer Science And Technology
Company: GreenDot School: Nanjing University of Aeronautics and

Industry: Banking Astronautics

Degree: Bachelor

Job Preferences

Function: System Architecture Design City: Shanghai

Target Salary: 3W-3.5W/Month Industry: Computer Services Online Game I

nternet/E-commerce

Function: Senior Software Engineer City: Shanghai

Target Salary: 3W-3.5W/Month Industry: Computer Services Online Game I

nternet/E-commerce

Job Type: Full-time

Job Type: Full-time

Current Status: I'm looking for jobs now Duty Time: within 1 month

Work Experience

2019/6-Present Sr. Software Engineer | API, COFO, etc.

GreenDot [2 year and 9 month]

Banking|500-1000|Foreign Comp.(Eur./N.Amer.)

Description: My Responsibility is design, develop and maintenance the code of legacy and baas platform. Like Web,

Web API, Transaction System, Secret Credit Card, UBER 2.0, Eureka, etc.

2018/6-2019/6 Software Engineer | HPS

Honeywell [1 year]

Computers, Software | ABOVE 10000 | Foreign Comp. (Eur./N.Amer.)

Description: HPS department is mainly responsible for Industrial Processing. My responsibility is focus on building th

e mobile solution for local & global projects. E.g. design & developing iOS app with swift, building the hy brid app like Cordova+Vue, Xamarin, etc. Developing some back-end service with .net core & .net techn

ology.

2015/9-2018/6 Software Engineer II | RISK Team

Green Dot Corporation [2 year and 9 month] Banking|500-1000|Foreign Comp.(Eur./N.Amer.)

Description: As a software engineer of Risk team. My main job is design & developing the risk internal system and in

tegrate the 3rd party system to verify the customer information and control the risk of customer's behavi

or.

2014/8-2015/8 Service Software Engineer | Cloudy BU

China Reading Limited [1 year]

Internet/E-commerce|1000-5000|Private Comp.

Description: Work for the Cloudy BU .Offer solutions for the android and ios developers , Develop and Test the 3G w

ebsite, Mobile Web and Web Api with C#. As a Software Engineer to give the solutions to the Client like

Android and IOS, and Report For Leader.

2013/1-2014/7 Internet/E-Commerce Software Engineer |IT Department

Emore Group [1 year and 6 month]

Internet/E-commerce|500-1000|Joint Ventures

Description: As a developer of internal IT department. My responsibility is developing internal systems of company. S

uch as IMS, managerment of exhibition.

Project Experience

2022/1-Present WorkflowShow

Description: Technology: Vue, C6, WebAPI, Automation Pipeline, T4, Docker, Workflow, Codeflow, Sagas

This project is drive by myself, the inspiration is become form the distributed transaction sagas from the financial architect and low-code platform. workflow show is the workflow engine which could deploy by c

ontainer and custom designed by UI. And also it support the Sagas.

The project is still demo step for now, it made up by 3 children projects: the SPA Web client which use C6 engine and Vue, the bridge project which based the T4 and transfer script, and the workflow engine project which will auto-generate code by config file and deploy by docker.

Responsibility:

The project is build by myself and it still demo for now. The technology skill include Vue, C6, WebAPI,au tomacation pipeline, T4,docker,workflow.codeflow.sagas.I will introduce the detail of this project in my p ersonal blog - blog.gethin.online.

2021/12-Present **Uber 2.0**

Related GreenDot

Company:

Description: Technology: .NET Core

The project is based in the original Uber system to migration to new Baas Platform and upgrade the pro duct. It include the data transfer, transaction integration, new client redo, new register and new transaction processor.

Responsibility: My responsibility is work on the API part, include new register processor, the data transfer and integrati

on Baas Platform.

2021/1-2021/10 Eureka SCC

Related GreenDot

Company:

Description: The product SCC is Secret Credit Card. It is based on the Baas Platform. This project is use for process

the Credit Card Business include the transaction system, auto money movement, split the bill, and notify

the customer consumption.

Responsibility: I major for develop the scc function like transaction, auto money movement, split the bill and notification.

2020/8-2021/1 Winback for Eureka

Related GreenDot

Company:

Description: Technology: VS2019, .NET Core, ActiveBatch

The "Eureka" Product which based on the Company Baas Platform need to migrate the old customers t o our new system and post the new cards of new product. The customer could active the new card to us e our new product.

This project is based on .net core as the development framework and go though to cover the BI File to PTS protocol file and send them to PTS to make the card, and get the status and card number for regis

ter service of internal projects. This system is designed for processing millions of data.

Responsibility: As the leader of this project, my responsibility is for the solution building, research and balance the solut

ion, import the data and integration the code of 3rd party.

2019/6-Present Gethin's Blog

Description: Technology: React, Docker, Azure Devops, Kubernetes, Netlify, HUGO, Github Action, Glthub page.

This project is the blog which use for recording my personal life and technology. It has been 3 version. T

he blog is driver by HUGO and Github action as CI & CD and host by Github Page.

The 1.0 version is based on Gatsby, and use the Azure Devops as the CI/CD and host by Azure Kubern etes Service. The blog is for summary the personal technology and focus on the cloud native ,kubernete s, python,etc

The 2.0 is based on the gatsby, the theme is use tinacms and netlify and the CI/CD and host by Netlify. Based on the React and AKS is hard for personal maintain.life is limit, keep it simple. So the 3.0 based on HUGO & LOVEIT & Github Page.

Responsibility:

The project is drive by myself and use for summary the technology and learn for new development skill. For now,I tried use the React, Azure Devops, Kubernetes, Netlify, HUGO, Github Action & Github Page.

2018/10- ADS Project

2018/12

Related Honeywell

Company:

Description: Technology: Cordova+Vue, Muti-UI, .Net Core, Docker, RabbitMQ, ORM, Specflow.

Honeywell ADS project is focus on building a whole solution which could push the alarm of Industrial to customers, and show the real-time core message.

The Project use the Event Driver Architecture style and use the docker+.net core+rabbitMQ+websocket to build the back-end service and use cordove+Vue to build the front-end hybrid mobile app.

Responsibility: My responsibility is research and choose the fit mobile solution & build the mobile solution framework &

build the C-S Realtime Communication solution & some parts of

the permission of service & Message Distribution. I use Cordova+Vue+Websocket to build the mobile h ybrid solution. And .net core + docker + RabbitMQ to build whole services.

2018/6-Present REFSAAS IOS APP

Related Honeywell

Company:

Description: Technology: XCode, Swift, Bitbucket, GameKit.

This Project is the mobile APP. As a part of IoT solution, the project should connect to the controller of r efrigerator and get the data of controller, it allow the customers change the data and upload the photo & note, submit the data, preview the data which submit.

This Project include: Connect & Parse the Controller, Customize Layout, Customize Components, Multil evel Menu, Drop-down Refresh, Take and Preview Photos & Notes, Submit Photos & Messages.

Responsibility: Integration Photo & Alarm Function, Write Dynamic Components, development some functions, use the

tool to make the app faster & solve the crash issues. Maintain and Refactoring the code of APP

2017/12-2018/6 Apple Pay Transfer (firewire)

Description: Technology: C#, WEB API, WCF, mock testing, sql server, team city, visual studio 2017

This project is cooperated with apple to implement apple pay transfer, green dot provide the bank servic e for apple (wave), and our team focus on the risk control.

Responsibility: As one developer of this project, my responsibility is doing some routine maintenance and development

work of firewire. And develop the functions which based on business requirement.

2017/4-2017/9 Integration Idology

Related GreenDot Corp corporation

Company:

Description: Technology: C#, WEB API, WCF,sql server,visual studio 2013

This project is use for verify the information of customer.we integrate idology for getting the information

of customer's documents like passport, ID card.

Responsibility: As main developer, I use the state machine to control the status and use the throttle for diversion. And I

integrate 6 internal productions. Cross-stack comments and E2E development.

2016/4-2016/8 integration mitek to id verification

Related GreenDot Corp corporation

Company:

Description: Technology: C#, WEB API, WCF, sql server, AngualJS, throttle, state machine, visual studio 2013

The mitek system integration is the whole E2E project. We use the system to verify the the information of customer and make the discussion to choose approval this people or decline. And as the main develop er and designer, I designed all of the processing of this system and integrate the render into our system. I introducing the new technology and idea like state machine and throttle and angularJS and web api and so on to make the solution work as well and greatly improve the effectiveness and reduce many bu

gs.

2015/7-2015/8 **ER-House System**

Description: Technology: C#, WPF, MVVM, sql server, visual studio 2015

The ER-House System is developed by my new team in pinganHouse by using WPF, and MVVM to be realized . This is a C/S System. I worked for the Examine Cases Module with VS Blend to Draw UI and $\rm d$

o work by prism.

Responsibility: I worked for the Examine Cases Module with VS Blend to Draw UI and do work by prism.

2015/3-2015/7 Routine works for 3G website and internal System

Description: Technology: C#, MVC, oracle, JavaScript, visual studio 2008.

Some routine works for 3G website and internal system, Change the Solution By MVC, and other work!

Responsibility: To develop some softwares and modules for 3G website

2015/1-2015/2 Activity for Spring Festival (Mobile Website)

Description: Technology: C#, CSS,JS,Jquery

1.Draw the UI of lottery.

2. Exchange Prize.

3. Receive the Coupons

4.the VIPs Subscribe Books

5. Adjust CSS and JS

Responsibility: Develop the system(Mobile Website) by myself to realize some modulars and adjust css .Evaluation co

mplexity, comment with other people and give the solutions to develop this.

2013/8-2013/10 **IMS**

Description: Technology: C#,VBA,share point, weboffice

IMS as the important projects in my company is a document's solution for institute in Emore Group . It's can edit document like excel and word online and comment with the office software to improve work effi

ciency.

Responsibility: I work as a Developer in our team to design the solution and give supports to this project, just like using

VBA and webOffice and so on.

Education

2009/9-2013/6 Nanjing University of Aeronautics and Astronautics

Bachelor|Computer Science And Technology

Description: In College, I learn about higher mathematics, probability, physics, the language of C, C++, Java, C#, m

icrocomputer principle and interface technology, network, database ,operating system ,software develop

ment technology and so on.

Graduate Info.

Leadership Position

2010/7-2011/6 The Leader of the secretary department

2010/6-2012/6 Literature and art committee member

Skills & Speciality (Including IT skills, languages, certifications and trainings)

Skills/Languages

C#.NETExpert
.NETExpert
C/C++Average
EnglishGood

JavaGood SQLAdvanced

SQL ServerAdvanced

Certifications

2010/1 **CET4**

Trainings

Institution: Microsoft

Description: The Html5's ecosystem of the Microsoft and Introduce some tools for developer like WinJs ,Ts ,Web Ap

p Template , the testing tools for Website and so on

Portfolio

Name: 移动开发者中级认证 View>

Name: ScrumMaster View>